tocktix.com 2019-05-12

# Tock - Privacy Policy

#### Last updated Oct 11, 2018

Tock, Inc. (“Tock,” “we,” or “us”) respects your privacy and is committed to protecting it through our compliance with this privacy policy (the “Privacy Policy”). This Privacy Policy describes the types of information, including personal information, that Tock may collect from you or users of your Tock account (collectively, “you” or “your”) or that you may provide when you visit www.exploretock.com, any predecessor or successor websites established by Tock which reference this Privacy Policy, and any Tock applications (collectively, the “Site”) or access or use the Tock reservation service offered through the Site (the “Service”). It also describes our practices for collecting, using, maintaining, protecting and disclosing that information.

This Privacy Policy applies both to persons who register or establish an account with Tock and to casual browsers of the Site. This Privacy Policy applies to information we collect on the Site and in email, text and other electronic messages between you and Tock. This Privacy Policy does not apply to information collected by Tock offline or by any third party, including through any application or content that may link to or be accessible from the Site.

This Privacy Policy is incorporated into and made a part of Tock’s Terms of Use.

#### Consent

By accessing or using the Site, you signify your consent to this Privacy Policy, including without limitation our use of cookies, tracking pixels and IP address logging, as discussed below. If you do not agree to this Privacy Policy, your choice is not to access or use the Site.

We may modify or update this Privacy Policy at any time in our sole discretion. We indicate at the top of the page when this Privacy Policy was last modified or updated. Your continued access or use of the Site following any modification or update constitutes and signifies your full acceptance of the changes.

If we make material changes to how we treat your information, we will notify you through a notice on the Site homepage and/or an email. You are responsible for periodically visiting the Site and this Privacy Policy to check for any changes.

#### Third Party Web Sites

If you click on a link to a third-party web site on the Site, including without limitation, any restaurant, bar, winery, or other customer of Tock (“Business”) web site, third-party payment processor web site or social network web site, you will leave the Site and go to the web site you selected. If you choose to share your information with any third-party website through buttons provided on the Site (e.g., you may share your reservation information on Facebook and Twitter), you will post such information to such third-party website outside of the Site. Because we cannot control the activities of third parties, including without limitation, Businesses, third-party payment processors and social networks, we are not responsible for any use of your information by such third parties, and we cannot guarantee that they will adhere to this Privacy Policy. If you visit or share your information with a third-party web site that is linked to the Site, you should consult that website’s privacy policy before providing any personal or other information.

#### What is personal information and when does Tock collect it?

Personal information is information by which you may be personally identified. Personal information may include your first and last name, e-mail address, phone number, mobile number, home or other physical address, birth date, credit card information, any information that permits you to be contacted physically or online and other personal information as defined under applicable law. Tock collects such personal information directly from you when you (i) use the Site or Service (including, but not limited to, when you register an account with Tock and enter information into your profile); (ii) make a reservation through the Site or Service; (iii) communicate via chats, conferences, and other avenues of communication on the Site; (iv) request further services from Tock or third parties on the Site; (v) participate in surveys, (vi) submit consumer complaints; (vii) correspond with Tock, including via email, text and other electronic messages; and (viii) conduct searches on the Site.

If you register for an account with Tock by using a third party, such as Google or Facebook, you are authorizing us to collect, maintain, and use pursuant to this Privacy Policy any information that you agreed such third party could provide to us in your privacy settings with such third party. You can modify your privacy settings with such third party.

We do not require personal information to gain access to the Site; however, you may not use certain features, products or services (including, without limitation, the Service) that require registration or receive certain materials unless such personal information is provided. You hereby consent to our collection of your personal information as outlined herein.

#### Online Chats and Conferences

As discussed above, you may choose to disclose information about yourself in chats, conferences, and other avenues of communication on the Site, if any. Such information is public information, and there is no expectation of privacy or confidentiality in either place. Please see our Terms of Use for additional guidelines about posting information on the Site.

#### What about cookies and other technologies?

Tock also uses automatic data collection technologies to collect information about your equipment, browsing actions and patterns as you navigate through the Site. Information collected by Tock through automatic data collection technologies includes, but is not limited to, details of your visits to the Site (e.g., traffic data, location data, logs and other communication data and the resources that you access and use on the Site) and information about your computer and internet connection (e.g., your Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, operating system and browser type). The technologies we use for this automatic data collection include, but are not limited to, cookies, local storage, tracking pixels, and IP address logging.

Cookies are small amounts of data downloaded to your computer to track movements and behavior within web sites. We may use cookies to deliver content specific to your interests and for other purposes. We may collect information on the frequency that certain digital activities are accessed, how much time is spent engaging certain informational content and which links are clicked. We may link cookie information to personal information.

Local storage is similar to cookies in that it is stored on your computer and can be used to store certain information about your activities and preferences.

Tracking pixels (a.k.a. beacons or tags) are small graphic images placed on a web page, web-based document or in an e-mail message. Tracking pixels are invisible to the user because they are typically very small (only 1-by-1 pixel) and the same color as the background of the web page, web-based document or e-mail message. We do not use tracking pixels to collect personal information about you. However, we may use tracking pixels to capture statistical usage information for the Site or features or other elements on the Site. We may link tracking pixel information to personal information to personalize user experience and for statistical analysis of user experiences on the Site.

Tock also maintains log files which contain IP addresses. An IP address is a numeric address that is assigned to your computer by your Internet Service Provider. In general, we only use log files to monitor traffic on the Site, to report aggregate information to our third-party providers, to troubleshoot technical problems and for statistical analyses and fraud and abuse prevention. In the event of user abuse of the Site, we may block certain IP addresses. IP addresses may be used to personally identify you in order to enforce our Terms of Use.

#### Other Information Collected

Certain activities will require you to create a username and password and provide other, non-personal information such as your month and day of birth, gender, preferences, etc. In addition, we may collect demographic information such as gender, zip code, information about your likes and dislikes, information about your current location, and other data that you may provide in surveys or online profiles. We may also link demographic information to personal information.

#### A Special Note About Children

The Site is not intended for children under 18 years of age. No one under age 18 may provide any information to or on the Site. We do not knowingly collect information from children under 18. If you are under 18, do not use or provide any information on the Site or on or through any of its features, register on the Site, make any purchases through the Site, use any of the features of the Site or provide any information about yourself to us, including your name, address, telephone number, email address, or any user name you may use. If we learn we have collected or received information from a child under 18, we will delete that information. If you believe we might have any information from or about a child under 18, please email our Privacy Officer at [privacy@tockhq.com](mailto:privacy@tockhq.com).

#### What happens to the information provided?

We use the information that we collect about you or that you provide to us, including any personal information, (i) to present the Site and its contents to you; (ii) to provide you with information, products or services that you request from us; (iii) to provide you with notices about your account; (iv) to carry out our obligations and enforce our rights arising from any contracts entered into between you and us, including for billing and collection; (v) to notify you about changes to the Site or the Service; (vi) to alert you to new developments, features and enhancements to the Site or Service and events of interest; (vii) to allow you to participate in the interactive features of the Site; (viii) to solicit feedback from you; (ix) to make updates to and to “debug” the Site or the Service; (x) to fulfill any purpose for which you provide it; and (xi) for any other purpose with your consent. We may contact you regarding third-party products or services; however, this does not mean that we have provided or traded your information to any party.

If you provide us with your email address and mobile phone number when you create an account or at any other time, you are expressly opting-in to receive email, SMS text messages, and push notifications from us relating to the Site and Services. You acknowledge that messaging and data rates may apply depending on your mobile phone service provider and that you are solely responsible for paying such rates.

If you opt-in to using location services for any Tock applications, we may collect and store information about your current location in order to enhance and customize your experience using such Tock applications (e.g., by showing you nearby Businesses).

We may use and disclose aggregated information about our users, and information that does not identify any individual, without restriction. We may disclose information that we collect or you provide as described in this Privacy Policy (i) to any subsidiaries and affiliates; (ii) for internal marketing and demographic studies; (iii) to our third-party providers (Businesses, third-party payment processors, strategic partners, third parties who deliver marketing messages and advertisements on our behalf, and third-party service providers); (iv) to a buyer or other successor in the event of a merger, divestiture, restructuring, reorganization, dissolution or other sale or transfer of some or all of Tock’s assets, whether as a going concern or as part of bankruptcy, liquidation or similar proceeding, in which information held by Tock about the Site is among the assets transferred; (v) to our investors; (vi) to fulfill any purpose for which you provide it; and (vii) to any other third parties with your consent. Because we cannot control the activities of the third parties listed above, we are not responsible for any use of your information by such third parties, and we cannot guarantee that they will adhere to this Privacy Policy.

We may also disclose your information (i) to enforce legal rights and comply with any court order, law or legal process, including to respond to any government or regulatory request; (ii) to enforce or apply our own Terms of Use and other agreements, including for billing and collection purposes; and (iii) if we believe disclosure is necessary or appropriate to protect the rights, property or safety of Tock, our customers or others. This includes exchanging information with third parties for the purposes of fraud protection and credit risk reduction.

#### Opt-Out Provision

If you would like to opt-out of having your personal information shared with parties outside of Tock, its affiliates, or its third-party providers, except to the extent required by law, court order, or as requested by other government or law enforcement authority, please email our Privacy Officer at [privacy@tockhq.com](mailto:privacy@tockhq.com).

If you’d like to have your name removed from our promotional mailing list or a Business’s promotional mailing list, please email our Privacy Officer at [privacy@tockhq.com](mailto:privacy@tockhq.com). You may also opt-out of promotional email messages from Tock or a Business by following the instructions contained within the emails sent to you by Tock or a Business, respectively.

You may opt-out of receiving SMS text messages from Tock or a Business at any time by emailing our Privacy Officer at [privacy@tockhq.com](mailto:privacy@tockhq.com).

You can use the settings on your mobile device to enable or turn off mobile push notifications from Tock and location services for any Tock applications.

Most browsers are automatically set to accept cookies whenever you visit a web site. You can disable cookies or set your browser to alert you when cookies are being sent; however, some areas of the Site will not function properly if you do so. To learn more about cookies and your options regarding their use, click here: [www.allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/).

At this time, we do not recognize or respond to any Do Not Track signals.

#### Where is the information held?

Currently, Tock maintains and stores your information on servers located within the United States. Therefore, your information may be transferred to, used, processed or held by Tock in the United States for the purposes set out in this Privacy Policy. If you are accessing the Site from outside the United States, please be advised that United States law may not offer the same privacy protections as the law of your jurisdiction. By using the Site, you understand and consent to the transfer to, use, processing and holding of your information on our servers in the United States and by those third parties with whom we share it as described in this Privacy Policy.

#### Safeguarding Your Information

We will only collect and use information in accordance with this Privacy Policy to the extent deemed reasonably necessary to serve our legitimate business purposes, and we will use commercially reasonable physical, managerial and technical safeguards to preserve the security, integrity, accuracy and privacy of the information you have provided. We will take reasonable steps to ensure that third parties to whom we transfer any information also use commercially reasonable safeguards.

The safety and security of your information also depends on you. To protect your Tock account, keep your account and password confidential. Do not share your account or password with anyone or reuse your Tock account password on third-party websites or applications. You are responsible for the activity that happens on or through your Tock account. We urge you to be careful about giving out information in any public areas of the Site. The information you share in public areas may be viewed by any user of the Site. If you learn of any unauthorized use of your password or Tock account, please email our Privacy Officer at [privacy@tockhq.com](mailto:privacy@tockhq.com).

Unfortunately, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to Tock. Any transmission of information is at your own risk. Once we receive your information, Tock uses commercially reasonable efforts to ensure the security of such information on our systems; however, we cannot guarantee that such information will not be accessed, disclosed, altered or destroyed by breach of any of our physical, managerial, technical or other safeguards.

If Tock learns of a security systems breach, we will use commercially reasonable efforts to notify you electronically so that you can take appropriate protective steps.

#### Review and Correction of Your Personal Information and Deletion of Your Account

We will retain your personal information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you with the Services. We may retain aggregated information about our users, and information that does not identify any individual, without restriction.

You may review and change your personal information by logging into the Site and visiting your account. You may also email our Privacy Officer at [privacy@tockhq.com](mailto:privacy@tockhq.com)to request access to, correct or delete any personal information that you have provided to us. We may not accommodate a request to change personal information if we believe the change would violate any law or legal requirement or cause the personal information to be incorrect.

You may delete your account by logging into the Site and visiting your account or by emailing our Privacy Officer at [privacy@tockhq.com](mailto:privacy@tockhq.com). Even if you delete your account, we may retain your personal information in our electronic data and other files and use your personal information as necessary to maintain the security, integrity and effective operation of the Site, to comply with our technical and legal obligations, to resolve disputes and enforce our agreements and policies, and to take other actions required or permitted by law. Deletion of your account will not remove your interactions with other Site users from the Site. If you have interacted with other users of the Site, including but not limited to transferring a reservation, such interactions may remain viewable in cached and archived pages, or might have been copied or stored by other users of the Site. In addition, if certain information has already been provided to third parties as described in this Privacy Policy, retention of that information will be subject to those third parties’ policies.

#### California Residents

As described in this Privacy Policy, Tock may share your personal information with third parties for such parties’ direct marketing purposes. Under California law, you may choose to opt out of Tock’s disclosure of personal information about you to third parties for direct marketing purposes. If you choose to opt-out at any time, please e-mail our Privacy Officer at [privacy@tockhq.com](mailto:privacy@tockhq.com).

#### Europe and UK Residents

Under Europe and UK law, Europe and UK residents have the right to access personal information Tock holds about them and information about how such personal information is being processed; request Tock to make changes necessary to ensure their personal information is accurate; request the deletion of their personal information; object to the processing of their personal information for any reason; and revoke any consent given with respect to personal information at any time. If you wish to exercise your rights, please e-mail our Privacy Officer at [privacy@tockhq.com](mailto:privacy@tockhq.com).

#### EU-US & Swiss-US Privacy Shield

Tock complies with the EU-US Privacy Shield Framework and the Swiss-US Privacy Shield Framework as set forth by the US Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal information transferred from the European Union and Switzerland to the United States, respectively. Tock has certified to the Department of Commerce that it adheres to the Privacy Shield Principles. If there is any conflict between the terms in this privacy policy and the Privacy Shield Principles, the Privacy Shield Principles shall govern. To learn more about the Privacy Shield program, and to view our certification, please visit [www.privacyshield.gov](https://www.privacyshield.gov/).

In compliance with the Privacy Shield Principles, Tock commits to resolve complaints about our collection or use of your personal information. European Union or Swiss individuals with inquiries or complaints regarding our Privacy Shield policy should first contact Tock at [privacy@tockhq.com](mailto:privacy@tockhq.com).

Tock has further committed to refer unresolved Privacy Shield complaints to JAMS, an alternative dispute resolution provider located in the United States. If you do not receive timely acknowledgment of your complaint from us, or if we have not resolved your complaint, you may contact or visit JAMS at [www.jamsadr.com/eu-us-privacy-shield](https://www.jamsadr.com/eu-us-privacy-shield) for more information or to file a complaint. The services of JAMS are provided at no cost to you.

If your complaint is not resolved by Tock or JAMS, you may, under certain conditions, invoke binding arbitration for complaints regarding Privacy Shield compliance. For more information, please see Annex 1, Section C of the E.U.-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework at [www.privacyshield.gov/article?id=ANNEX-I-introduction](https://www.privacyshield.gov/article?id=ANNEX-I-introduction).

In the context of an onward transfer, a Privacy Shield organization has responsibility for the processing of personal information it receives under the Privacy Shield and subsequently transfers to a third party acting as an agent on its behalf. The Privacy Shield organization shall remain liable under the Privacy Shield Principles if its agent processes such personal information in a manner inconsistent with the Privacy Shield Principles, unless the organization proves that it is not responsible for the event giving rise to the damage.

The Federal Trade Commission has jurisdiction over Tock’s compliance with the Privacy Shield.

#### Questions About This Privacy Policy

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or the privacy practices of this Site, please email our Privacy Officer at [privacy@tockhq.com](mailto:privacy@tockhq.com).
